<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/Astoria_MR_NW.xml</id><title>Astoria_MR_NW</title><updated>2019-01-22T13:49:21-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/Astoria_MR_NW.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in Astoria_MR_NW</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/que/fee/d/astoria-long-island-city-living-lrg/6800916233.html</id><title>$2645  //  *Long Island City Living!* Lrg Bdrms Lrg Lvng Spce w/  Elev. Ldry Bldg</title><updated>2019-01-22T07:37:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00D0D_h418ZUE2EIW_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;Make Astoria your new home after seeing this newly renovated TRUE two- bedroom apartment. This unit features an open kitchen with modern appliances including dishwasher, granite counter tops. The living room is a great space, perfect for entertaining your guest or just lounging around on the couch watching television or reading a book. Both bedrooms can easily accommodate a full to queen size bed, plus additional furniture and has a built in closet for additional storage space. Gleaming hardwood floors, marble bathroom, laundry facilities , live in super and walking distance to the train makes this place a must see!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking for great food or exotic microbrews? Look no further than Astoria! This northern Queens neighborhood exudes a youthful charm and welcoming attitude. Mom-and-pop shops snuggle up to humble townhouses whose residents address one another by name. With appreciative ease of commute to midtown; under 20 minutes, this laid-back neighborhood's various culinary destinations and quiet streets make it the ideal alternative to expensive city living.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact me to view this unit right away!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian Robles- Se Habla Espanol&lt;br&gt;(860)-578-7677&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Rainey&lt;br&gt;(646)520-8945&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact me for more info.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, I have apartments throughout Manhattan, Hell's Kitchen, Clinton, Midtown West, Midtown, Midtown East, Upper Westside, Upper Eastside, Chelsea, Flatiron, and Upper Manhattan. Doorman &amp;amp; Brownstone bldgs with outdoor space, patios, balcony, laundry &amp;amp; more. If this isn't your ideal place, let me know and I'm certain I can find it!    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00b0b_IvoKXhHFqF_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01515_hAB30w2ESXa_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00I0I_D35vsrqSLI_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00B0B_isK2BagoQ5U_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00707_hd0di7fQkxv_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00R0R_1GVHs5wUfdI_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01010_g54RV74zxuz_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/que/fee/d/astoria-long-island-city-living-lrg/6800916233.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-22T07:37:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>