<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/CarollGardens_CobbleHill_F.xml</id><title>CarollGardens_CobbleHill_F</title><updated>2019-01-12T00:38:02-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/CarollGardens_CobbleHill_F.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in CarollGardens_CobbleHill_F</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/brooklyn-carroll-gardens-1-bedroom/6792362315.html</id><title>$2200  //  Carroll Gardens 1 Bedroom + Office with Tin Ceiling and Pet Friendly!</title><updated>2019-01-11T11:32:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00g0g_iIAJfggjFiA_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;(Listing ID: cl-130853.1) (718) 930-7999&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;To view our walk through video, please visit our website at: http://destinationrealestate.com/listing?listing=9139-cl&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a 1 Bedroom + Office in the Carroll Gardens area of Brooklyn. The Apartment Features Tin Ceilings, Celing Fans, Hardwood Floors, Plently of Closet Space, Tile Backsplash in the Kitchen, and Original Details (Including a Fireplace Mantle with Exposed Brick!). Includes Heat, and Hot Water. Dogs and Cats Accepted on Approval.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedroom 17x11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Office Space 12.5 x 6&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Living Room 16.5x11.5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kitchen Area 16.5x11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This apartment gives you great access to the downtown Brooklyn Nightlife scene as well as quick access into Red Hook, Gowanus, and Cobble Hill. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy local Parks and Greeneries, such as Red Hook Park and Recreation Center, Carroll Park and the Smith Street Stage, Cough Triangle, and St. Marie's Playground. Local attractions and stores include: The Gowanus Ballroom and the Gowanus Loft, Rooftop Films, Shipwrecked Miniature Golf, and Oculus 20/20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Local restaurants and bars include: Other Half Brewing Company, Take A Break &amp;amp; I'll Bake Cafe &amp;amp; Creperie, Frankies 457 Spuntino, and Travel Bar. Local emergency stations include: FDNY Engine 279/Ladder 131 located on Lorraine Street and Smith Street. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carroll Gardens also includes dozens of bike paths for easy travel.Subway access to the F and G trains at the Carroll Street Station. Roughly 30 minute commute into Midtown Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Walk Time to Nearest Train Stations&lt;/u&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carroll St (5 mins):     F, G&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Where is this apartment in relation to other neighborhoods?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;South&lt;/strong&gt; of Cobble Hill, Boerum Hill, Brooklyn Heights, Downtown Brooklyn, and Fort Greene&lt;br&gt;                &lt;strong&gt;East&lt;/strong&gt; of Red Hook and Columbia Waterfront District&lt;br&gt;                &lt;strong&gt;West&lt;/strong&gt; of Gowanus, Park Slope, and Prospect Heights&lt;br&gt;All apartments listed on this website have a broker's fee unless otherwise indicated. All information presented on thissite regarding real property, for sale, purchase, rental and/or financing is from sources deemed reliable. No warranty orrepresentation is made as to the accuracy thereof and same is submitted subject to errors, omissions, change of price, rentals or other conditions, prior sale, lease or financing or withdrawal without notice. All dimensions and squarefootage are approximate. For the most exact dimensions and square footage please hire your own architect or engineer.We are an equal housing opportunity provider.  We do not discriminate on the basis of race, creed, color, national origin,sexual orientation, lawful source of income, military status, sex, gender identity, age, disability, familiar status (having children under age 18), or religion.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00h0h_3bbgVbFStpL_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00d0d_kb64GCdA66I_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00g0g_8m0MgdNkjRG_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00d0d_jlvoYwisPqi_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00v0v_f4WocBS65kW_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00808_lcdFuJMvjlI_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00Y0Y_7wDZGmoAwc0_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00303_355g0UGYlD9_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01010_d32l54Mosvl_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00q0q_lE4TtjJPPzQ_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00B0B_dQPRK2DZmBm_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01515_8C1K39NAjwe_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00B0B_h3myorDX74x_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00202_b1ZDFXX8Bnv_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00y0y_dGRNBRIwuPW_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/brooklyn-carroll-gardens-1-bedroom/6792362315.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-11T11:32:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>