<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/CarollGardens_CobbleHill_F.xml</id><title>CarollGardens_CobbleHill_F</title><updated>2018-08-04T12:28:17-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/CarollGardens_CobbleHill_F.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in CarollGardens_CobbleHill_F</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/ohpm-1-bed-shared-garden/6661002389.html</id><title>$2200  //  OH (08/04) 12-1pm 1 bed w/ Shared Garden.  Close to Cobble Hill Park</title><updated>2018-08-03T11:32:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00W0W_1QH2IVLd1LH_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;September 1st  move-in!   THIS APARTMENT IS IN THE RARE and overlooks a quiet garden and you will forget that Hicks is out the front door of the building. It is available for the first time in 7 years. Open living and dining room contains hardwood floors, exposed brick and great Eastern sun exposure. Kitchen includes a dishwasher with great cabinetry. Bedroom can fit a queen sized bed and includes a closet. There is an area off of the kitchen that could be used for a dining or an office. There is a quiet garden where you could have a dinner party and is shared.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Located in Cobble Hill you will be close to the retail and shopping on Court and the dining on Smith. Just a few blocks from the Brooklyn Greenway that will take you to Brooklyn Bridge Park Pier 6 where you can now catch the NYC Ferry. Close to F,G at Bergen and 2,3,4,5 and R at Borough Hall. Pets only on approval.&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00D0D_96b5zgoqqnb_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00F0F_1E5xkK03Why_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00x0x_8FCVbmRafbx_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00H0H_7i5T1MMFP4e_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01515_diYeG1sOMgF_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/ohpm-1-bed-shared-garden/6661002389.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-08-03T11:32:00-05:00</published></entry><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/cobble-hill-1-bedroom-high/6661002567.html</id><title>$2500  //  Cobble Hill 1 Bedroom w High Ceilings, Eat-In kitchen, Orig. Details!</title><updated>2018-08-03T11:32:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00N0N_fDjAMQouzKk_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;(Listing ID: cl-130808.2) (718) 930-7999&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;To view our walk through video, please visit our website at: http://destinationrealestate.com/listing?listing=8843-cl&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a 1 Bedroom in the Cobble Hill area of Brooklyn. The Apartment Features Hardwood Floors, Exposed Brick, Original Details, High Ceilings, Decorative Fireplace, Ceiling Fan, Eat-in-Kitchen, Living Room, Freezer, Refrigerator, and Range / Oven. Includes Heat, and Hot Water. Dogs and Cats Accepted on Approval.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cobble Hill Features the Urban Meadow, South Brooklyn Children's garden, Human Compass Garden, Clay works on Columbia, Brooklyn Collective, Beam Center, Smith Street Community Garden, Jalopy Theatre and School of Music, Brooklyn Public Library,  Short walk to the historic Cobble Hill Cinemas, Trader Joes, Carroll Park, Van Voorhees Playground and Brooklyn Bridge Park with great views of Manhattan, Cobble Hill also features many local grocery stores, bars, cafes, and restaurants. Great place for a bike ride with tons of bike paths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Short walk to the F and G trains at the Carroll Street Station. Access to the R train by transferring to 4th Avenue (3 stops). Roughly 30 minute commute into Midtown Manhattan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interior Dimensions:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Living Room 12x10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kitchen 15x11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedroom 13.5x12&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Where is this apartment in relation to other neighborhoods?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;North&lt;/strong&gt; of Carroll Gardens, Gowanus, and Red Hook&lt;br&gt;                &lt;strong&gt;South&lt;/strong&gt; of Brooklyn Heights, Downtown Brooklyn&lt;br&gt;                &lt;strong&gt;East&lt;/strong&gt; of Columbia Waterfront District&lt;br&gt;                &lt;strong&gt;West&lt;/strong&gt; of Boerum Hill, Park Slope, Prospect Heights and Fort Greene&lt;br&gt;All apartments listed on this website have a broker's fee unless otherwise indicated. All information presented on thissite regarding real property, for sale, purchase, rental and/or financing is from sources deemed reliable. No warranty orrepresentation is made as to the accuracy thereof and same is submitted subject to errors, omissions, change of price, rentals or other conditions, prior sale, lease or financing or withdrawal without notice. All dimensions and squarefootage are approximate. For the most exact dimensions and square footage please hire your own architect or engineer.We are an equal housing opportunity provider.  We do not discriminate on the basis of race, creed, color, national origin,sexual orientation, lawful source of income, military status, sex, gender identity, age, disability, familiar status (having children under age 18), or religion.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00h0h_l6x3PvXCEt1_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01212_gzoBZdNKmBH_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00Q0Q_fyrbBZaNRjN_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00r0r_jXDQrOy0f6g_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00c0c_k7PnoLkFhDR_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01010_h7PuhnaU6Ig_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01616_aTzqKol8BEA_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00c0c_hgGQzbgnF4Z_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00B0B_fulkfMhsQXr_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00B0B_d7tKn1yR50R_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00s0s_boNCFfIdjvW_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00808_4mvXsbOSOTT_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00909_8PIROJBxQub_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00909_1B07aFZJD3u_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01313_dEd6HdzN9kX_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/cobble-hill-1-bedroom-high/6661002567.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-08-03T11:32:00-05:00</published></entry><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/ohpm-1-bed-shared-garden/6661004925.html</id><title>$2200  //  OH (08/31) 12-1pm 1 bed w/ Shared Garden.  Close to Cobble Hill Park</title><updated>2018-08-03T11:34:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00f0f_K3SsWg2jTH_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;​ You will not lack Vitamin D in this space!  One bedroom Loft space with floor to ceiling windows.  Located on top floor this sun dreched space is the perfect spot for entertaining.  Features include high ceilings, exposed brick, hardwood floors throughout, and a lofted area for the bed and dresser.  The kitchen includes a dishwasher.  Bathroom includes a tub and a skylight.  Tired of looking at cookie cutter renovations or railroads.  Come home to this spacious loft. There is a well-maintained shared garden downstairs.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Located in Cobble Hill you will be near the F,G at Bergen. A block away from Pok, Pok and the Greenway to Brooklyn Bridge Park. Near all the amenities on Court and dining on Smith.  This is a spot not to be missed. Heat and Hot Water included.  Pets on approval.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00x0x_60Xk2DEOzhb_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01515_fIl88uAluLp_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00101_gGjt2v4ldFd_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00c0c_kY9eqDVDAP1_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/ohpm-1-bed-shared-garden/6661004925.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-08-03T11:34:00-05:00</published></entry><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/apartment-for-rentboerum-hill/6661069113.html</id><title>$2500  //  Apartment for rent*Boerum Hill, Brooklyn*no brokers fee</title><updated>2018-08-03T13:55:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00K0K_loP9LXSQrk0_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;rent  $2500&lt;br&gt;Move in date is flexible, as we take time to clean,paint,and varnish the floors. 1 Bedroom with walk in closet, and a smaller junior room with closet, that can be used as a bedroom or writing room, located on 2nd floor of owner occupied brownstone on Wyckoff street  (between Hoyt and Bond) historical district  in Boerum Hill, Brooklyn. Well cared for original wood floors located throughout apartment, eat-in-kitchen, dishwasher, new refrigerator,.Marble mantlepiece in living room with exposed brick wall. Landlord pays heat and hot water. Near restaurants, shopping, and 2  blocks from the F , G trains, and a short distance from Barclays/Atlantic Ave. station.  Potential tenant must have proof of employment/work reference, and a recent credit report. Typical approval standards call for verifiable income 40 times the rental amount. One month rent plus one month security deposit is required. Offering a one year lease at this time. Cats ok&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00e0e_2tZphM6j5Q9_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00X0X_8w4FzCGaZUj_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00G0G_llaBaDhYBxo_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00Z0Z_hghcqyoFLg_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00J0J_9ED4vX4bswi_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/apartment-for-rentboerum-hill/6661069113.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-08-03T13:55:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>