<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ClintonHill_BedStudy_AC.xml</id><title>ClintonHill_BedStudy_AC</title><updated>2018-08-09T16:22:21-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ClintonHill_BedStudy_AC.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in ClintonHill_BedStudy_AC</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/11-month-lease-renovated/6666602799.html</id><title>$1875  //  11 month lease renovated &amp;amp; updated 1 bedroom Brownstone apartment</title><updated>2018-08-09T15:58:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00N0N_bkYhIzAjtiR_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;It took us a while to find this updated one bedroom in Bed-Stuy (on the border of Crown Heights and Clinton Hill) . Only giving it up because we're moving coasts! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The details: renovated one-bedroom apartment on the second floor of a brownstone on a quiet street. Building is quiet, only a few apartments in the building, with young professionals. High ceilings, wood floors, stainless steel appliances (oven, fridge, small dishwasher, microwave), updated bathroom, tub. Boasts a cool almost floor length vintage mirror which makes the space look bigger and reflects the light in the afternoon. View of the downstairs yard. There is no access to the yard, but you can sit on the small fire escape or look at it outside your bedroom window. It's peaceful. Coin laundry in the basement, very convenient.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Logistics: We re-signed a year lease one month ago, so you'd be signing an 11-month lease with Brooklyn Rents. We've not had any problems with the management company and they are reputable (they have 4.4 stars on google- I learned the hard way from other apartments to look these ratings up). Rent is 1875 per month (we negotiated this rate, as they wanted to raise it) and you can pay them online or at the office which is a 10 min walk away. You will take over the lease, which means they will ask for your paystubs, tax returns, etc and ask that you make 40x the rent, or have a guarantor who makes 80x the rent. Application cost is $100 per applicant ($100 for a guarantor as well), and due at the lease is first, last, and security deposit. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recap:&lt;br&gt;Hardwood and tiled floors throughout&lt;br&gt;High ceiling&lt;br&gt;Exposed brick&lt;br&gt;Granite kitchen counter top &lt;br&gt;Newly renovated kitchen with SS appliances with dishwasher&lt;br&gt;Full bathroom with soaking tub and vanity&lt;br&gt;Living room for entertaining guests&lt;br&gt;Lots of natural sunlight&lt;br&gt;Laundry in building&lt;br&gt;11 Month lease&lt;br&gt;NO FEE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;View by appointment, starting on 8/10. For 9/1 move-in (or can be as early as 8/20). Flexible. Serious inquiries only.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;List of cool spots nearby:&lt;br&gt;Cute cafés (Furman's, Ian's, Golda, Corner Grind)&lt;br&gt;Heal Haus (for yoga, meditation &amp;amp; wellness)&lt;br&gt;Le Paris Dakar creperie and coffee&lt;br&gt;Wholesome foods market/deli&lt;br&gt;Indian, Senegalese, Japanese, West Indian restaurants around&lt;br&gt;ArtShack Brooklyn (ceramics classes)&lt;br&gt;Post office, Walgreens, 7-Eleven &lt;br&gt;David's Brisket House (Bk version of Katz)&lt;br&gt;Heritage Tonsorial barber shop&lt;br&gt;Planet Fitness&lt;br&gt;SuperfoodTown grocery&lt;br&gt;Bedford branch public library&lt;br&gt;&amp;amp; more&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subway A, C Nostrand, or C Franklin&lt;br&gt;Buses: B-44, B-44/SBS, B25, B49    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01111_e4oJrW5zIxB_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00P0P_eBYtXctBTXr_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00J0J_hd48I1BePeo_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00r0r_gyv0WaZZkMS_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00B0B_2Zof3Zblfbq_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00505_gzbZ6UTuALT_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00X0X_h0vyuotHBRx_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00606_6nLOqzQgYqF_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01212_1oR8GTJKeA0_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00F0F_iPVIMuxkLob_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00x0x_gHoU4IKI5Eg_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00y0y_4aqlMpkxOjc_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00909_dkCdiUjPyVm_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/11-month-lease-renovated/6666602799.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-08-09T15:58:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>