<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ClintonHill_BedStudy_AC.xml</id><title>ClintonHill_BedStudy_AC</title><updated>2019-01-21T00:09:40-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ClintonHill_BedStudy_AC.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in ClintonHill_BedStudy_AC</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/brooklyn-amazing-furnished-1-bdrm/6799708574.html</id><title>$2600  //  Amazing Furnished 1 Bdrm Apartments</title><updated>2019-01-20T17:51:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00h0h_3b3yi8RcZYj_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!BOOK NOW ONLY $2600 !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br&gt;!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!BOOK NOW ONLY $2600 !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br&gt;!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!BOOK NOW ONLY $2600 !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This beautiful apt comes with many of the original details, along with updated kitchen, appliances, and bathroom. The master bedroom has a queen size bed and the living room has a couch that pulls out to a comfortable full size bed perfect for 2 kids of one adult.&lt;br&gt;Sheets, towels, wifi, TV, and all utilities are included.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Located in the heart of the thriving historic district of Stuyvesant Heights. A beautiful community of brownstone houses in Brooklyn- with many local boutiques and eateries in the area for your convenience. A short walk are shops on Lewis avenue. This includes Peaches, a sit-down restaurant offering the best in American comfort food. For dessert right across from this brownstone you can savor a healthy treat of frozen yogurt from the newly opened Brooklyn Swirl. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooklyn is also home to many other charming neighborhoods with thriving cultural institutions. The Fulton Street A and C subway station is only a five minute walk from the brownstone, easily leading you to your destinations. The newly built Barclays Center which provides some of the best in world class entertainment is a short 15-minutes drive, or 10-minute subway ride via the C train.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also a 15-minute drive will bring you to the historic Brooklyn Museum. Right next door for further exploration is the Botanical Gardens, Grand Army Plaza Library, and the largest park in the borough, Prospect Park. Of course while you're in New York City, you'll want to explore Manhattan. Your stay is only a 20-minutes subway ride away via the A express train. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For an experience that is cozy yet close to the high paced excitement of the city, this is the perfect place to stay.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENT THIS AMAZING TRUE2BR APARTMENT TODAY, GREAT VALUE!&lt;br&gt;FOR MORE INFORMATION PLEASE CONTACT&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AVAILABLE NOW TILL MAY 12&lt;br&gt;AVAILABLE NOW TILL MAY 12&lt;br&gt;AVAILABLE NOW TILL MAY 12&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENTAL FEATURES: Living room - Master bath - Microwave - Refrigerator - Stove/Oven - Ceiling fans - Central heat - High-speed internet - On-street parking - Fireplace &lt;br&gt;LEASE TERMS &lt;br&gt;1 - 12 Months Lease.&lt;br&gt;Credit Check Fee $25&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00n0n_4S2T77xwgLj_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00p0p_iAs9DfHqICC_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00h0h_edWr8KgefUM_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00I0I_kcLg90Y5eHh_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00Y0Y_gXX6ahnzdGt_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01717_gBm85obZcrh_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01717_ikCrisRuILY_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00P0P_anY2l0ccweR_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00W0W_cSCTyPJeNfK_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/brooklyn-amazing-furnished-1-bdrm/6799708574.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-20T17:51:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>