<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/Greenwood_DR.xml</id><title>Greenwood_DR</title><updated>2019-01-19T18:47:48-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/Greenwood_DR.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in Greenwood_DR</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/brooklyn-sunset-park-1-bedroom/6798863604.html</id><title>$1725  //  Sunset Park 1 Bedroom W/ Dishwasher, Granite Countertop, Cats Approved</title><updated>2019-01-19T12:43:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00b0b_a1NrBNUmEYL_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;(Listing ID: cl-130863.1) (718) 930-7999&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;To view our walk through video, please visit our website at: http://destinationrealestate.com/listing?listing=9199-cl&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a 1 Bedroom in the Sunset Park area of Brooklyn. Building Features Laundry. The Apartment Features Hardwood Floor, Stainless Steel Appliances (Dishwasher, Stove, Microwave, Fridge), Tile Flooring, Tile Backsplash, and Granite Countertop. Includes Heat, and Hot Water. Cats Accepted on Approval.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Detailed Photos Coming Soon!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Living Area 13.5x10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kitchen 13x6&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedroom 11.5x8&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunset Park Features a rich cultural base and background that the neighborhood is known for. Sunset Park also features the local staple in Industry City, giving you quick access to tons of local shops inside the enormous warehouses that built Sunset Park into the neighborhood it is today. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy local Parks and Greeneries such as Sunset Park and the Sunset Park Pool, Industry City, Bush Terminal Piers Park, Pier 4, Rappaport Playground, Alben Triangle, Brooklyn Army Terminal, and Gonzalo Plasencia Park. Local attractions and stores include the Five Borough Brewing, Brooklyn Hangar, Tabla Rasa Gallery, Melody Lanes Bowling Center, Sunset Park Library, Costco, 100 Fun Karaoke Bar and the Brooklyn Nets Training Center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;20 minute train ride to parks and attractions such as the historic Alpine Cinemas, Owl's Head Park, Narrows Botanical Gardens, and Prospect Park. Nearby health centers and emergency include FDNY EMS Station 40, Maimonides Medical Center and NYU Langone Hospital - Brooklyn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunset Park also includes dozens of bike paths for easy travel.Subway access to the D, N, and R trains at the 36th Street station. Commute is 40 minutes into Midtown Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunset Park also gives you access to Greenwood, Borough Park, and Bay Ridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Where is this apartment in relation to other neighborhoods?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;North&lt;/strong&gt; of Bay Ridge&lt;br&gt;                &lt;strong&gt;South&lt;/strong&gt; of Greenwood and Park Slope&lt;br&gt;                &lt;strong&gt;West&lt;/strong&gt; of Borough Park, Dyker Heights, and Bensonhurst&lt;br&gt;All apartments listed on this website have a broker's fee unless otherwise indicated. All information presented on thissite regarding real property, for sale, purchase, rental and/or financing is from sources deemed reliable. No warranty orrepresentation is made as to the accuracy thereof and same is submitted subject to errors, omissions, change of price, rentals or other conditions, prior sale, lease or financing or withdrawal without notice. All dimensions and squarefootage are approximate. For the most exact dimensions and square footage please hire your own architect or engineer.We are an equal housing opportunity provider.  We do not discriminate on the basis of race, creed, color, national origin,sexual orientation, lawful source of income, military status, sex, gender identity, age, disability, familiar status (having children under age 18), or religion.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00z0z_53Xj1JX7VC_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00k0k_dHtqpYegXky_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00b0b_a2AJlbM7EaN_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00202_9pSNcYvnaz1_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00K0K_5A6QuiZiWW7_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00C0C_jrmFe09tDqg_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00a0a_jrFteaIGRip_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00S0S_auDZ3raqknn_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01313_kOGM3qWMRBI_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00101_cSyDhU5RBmy_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/fee/d/brooklyn-sunset-park-1-bedroom/6798863604.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-19T12:43:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>