<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/LowerUpperEast_6_NQ.xml</id><title>LowerUpperEast_6_NQ</title><updated>2018-08-07T15:16:58-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/LowerUpperEast_6_NQ.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in LowerUpperEast_6_NQ</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/mnh/nfb/d/delightful-1-bedroom-apt-with/6664714551.html</id><title>$2010  //  DELIGHTFUL 1 Bedroom Apt with Exquisite 4,000 SF EUROPEAN GARDEN</title><updated>2018-08-07T14:51:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00T0T_atWGTJufTOS_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Was it the robin in the trees in the morning or the neighboring leaves that first touched my heart when I entered this Apartment?" &lt;br&gt;- Catherine (resident of the building) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a NEW Listing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Apartment has WONDERFUL VIEWS OVERLOOKING the GARDEN with a LIGHT and AIRY FEELING throughout the Apartment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXTRAORDINARY EUROPEAN GARDEN &lt;br&gt;Wake up to the SOUNDS of NATURE. This Apartment comes with ACCESS To An EXQUISITE 4,000 Square Foot EUROPEAN GARDEN. This Apartment has wonderful garden views. For those who love nature, the Garden (with its vibrant Hydrangas, Rhodadendrum, Azelias, Roses and Lillies) will touch your heart. The garden has Tables and Chairs for outdoor dining. During the Spring, Fall and Summer months ... the Garden is a special place to have meals, read a good book, or simply work on your laptop computer. We have a communal HERB GARDEN, for tenants who like to cook, which provides a fine selection of fresh Basil, French Tarragon, Verbane, Oregano, Mint, Corriander, Parsley, Dill, Chives, Rosemary, Sage and Thyme. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCELLENT UPPER EASTSIDE NEIGHBORHOOD - Located on East 70th Street (between 1st and 2nd Avenues) Located in One of MANHATTAN'S FINEST NEIGHBORHOODS in close proximity to Central Park, Museum Mile, Lincoln Center, Time Square, Madison Avenue, Sloan Kettering, Rockefeller University, New York Hospital, and the United Nations. EXCELLENT ACCESS to PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION with fast commutes to SoHo, Greenwich Village, Chelsea, Tribeca, Wall Street, Upper Westside, Chinatown and Little Italy. This Apartment is located 4 1/2 Blocks from the Hunter College / 68th Street Subway Station and 2 Blocks from the Cross Town Bus Stops. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENT STABILIZED APARTMENT &lt;br&gt;The Breakdown of the Rent is as follows: $2,010 + $90 (for Electric + Gas Utilities) = A TOTAL RENT of $2,100 per month (which includes ALL UTILITIES). This is a Preferential Discounted Rent. Fair Market Value for this Apartment is approximately $2,600.  Air Conditioning is prorated at $28 extra per month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AVAILABLE: August 15  - September 1, 2018&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPOINTMENTS to PREVIEW APARTMENT:&lt;br&gt;If you would like to schedule an appointment to preview this apartment, please contact Hara by E-MAIL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DESCRIPTION OF APARTMENT &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o CHARACTER Spacious Railroad One Bedroom Apartment (400 square feet) which is ideally suited for a single person or a couple. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o HIGH 13 FOOT CEILINGS + 2 Large Windows. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Exquisite GARDEN VIEWS and Natural Lighting.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Beautiful ORIGINAL HARDWOOD FLOORS and MANTEL for displaying your favorite possessions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; o 3rd Floor Apartment  in a walk up building &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Quiet and Peaceful Apartment &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Bedroom Closet + Old Fashioned Pantry + Storage Hutch above kitchen&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Galley Kitchen with Microwave, Stove, and 1/2 Refrigerator.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Bathroom with full bath / shower and black and white tiles. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Beautiful RECENTLY RENOVATED HALLWAYS in robin's egg blue with cobalt accents.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Rated the Safest Neighborhood in Manhattan by the New York Police Department. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Off Premises Laundry in the Building Next Door &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Excellent Selection of Gourmet Speciality Stores and Fine Restaurants throughout the Neighborhood. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Post Office located in the Neighborhood 1 Block Away &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AVAILABLE: August 15 - September 1 Lease Date&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PET FRIENDLY&lt;br&gt;Landlord will allow a cat; NO dogs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCELLENT UPPER EAST SIDE NEIGHBORHOOD &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Located near Central Park, Museum Mile, Lincoln Center, Time Square, Madison Avenue, Sloan Kettering, Rockefeller University, and New York Hospital. Great access to public transportation with fast commutes to SoHo, Greenwich Village, Chelsea, Tribeca, Wall Street &amp;amp; Upper Westside. This Refined Upper East Side Neighborhood is considered to be the safest neighborhood in Manhattan. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOD LANDLORD &lt;br&gt;Landlord is looking for a Responsible, Considerate, High Integrity individual with a Secure Source of Income and Good Credit History. Landlord will rent to individuals with a solid co-signor.  If you meet these qualifications, please contact Hara by e-mail or phone (917) 526-2466. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONTACT INFORMATION: &lt;br&gt;If you meet these qualifications, please CONTACT Hara by preferably by E-MAIL by clicking the REPLY Tab in this listing.  When responding to this listing, please include the following information: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Your Name / Names: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Your Cellphone Number: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Your E-mail Address: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Current Place of Residence (City, State or Country) (so that we know which Time Zone you are in for purposes of calling you back): &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Your Move In Date: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Whether you will require a Co-Signor for the lease: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Time and Date you would like to preview the Apartment: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00G0G_e4hAQvNN3J4_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00101_43VzHBZmx5c_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00606_893JwztLslc_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00R0R_5jgduciKH9r_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01111_8Yr4yBq3tq7_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00c0c_9FMviZwDfdi_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00S0S_cJNk101GbN8_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00O0O_4fIrkJJWQka_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00505_3ZtVoIUSyH4_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00E0E_5gIBT3z7Y27_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01515_6oJ2K4GuPiP_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00T0T_5VQxU5gimpT_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00s0s_jb88X7m9SLl_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00D0D_cKM1HiqlmYF_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00n0n_6n3NJBkqbze_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00606_c9mvXdTlzZv_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00t0t_lYuETAG2bdH_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00000_kPz4p5gdFUK_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00z0z_liS9r73odOd_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/mnh/nfb/d/delightful-1-bedroom-apt-with/6664714551.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-08-07T14:51:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>