<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/LowerEast_F_BD.xml</id><title>LowerEast_F_BD</title><updated>2018-08-05T09:06:02-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/LowerEast_F_BD.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in LowerEast_F_BD</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/mnh/abo/d/furnished-large-1-bedroom-apt/6657091517.html</id><title>$2250  //  Furnished Large 1 Bedroom Apt in Lower East Side</title><updated>2018-08-05T08:56:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00Q0Q_7L6LTi9flLC_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hello.&lt;br&gt;I will be renting my wonderful furnished apartment.  Furnishings are primarily from Crate and Barrel.  The apartment boasts over 1,000 square feet of living space, beautifully furnished by local New York City interior decorator. The building is off the main drag and hustle of the LES but conveniently located to all restaurants, bars, and transportation.  Just a 6-minute walk to the Delancey stop on the F-M-J lines, many busses, and CitiBike is conveniently located right outside the apartment door!&lt;br&gt;The space is a ground level secluded true one bedroom with den area, large living space, kitchen, and bath. &lt;br&gt;The building hosts a laundry room on the ground level with a large outdoor private courtyard. Additionally, the roof was remodeled last year, which is great for panoramic NYC views of the Empire State Building down to the World Trade Center.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;More pictures available if interested.  To weed out spammers please state, "more pics LES" in your subject header.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reason I can offer this place at such a reduced price is due to the fact that I will be living between philly and NyC for awhile and will need to stay occasionally. The apartment boasts an extra nook which would be my accommodations. I know it may sound strange but the benefit is that you'll get a wonderful furnished apartment, dirt cheap!!..and have it a majority of time. &lt;br&gt;As for me, I currently attend NYU where I'm pursuing my PhD. &lt;br&gt; I'm available for any questions or to show the apartment and discuss.&lt;br&gt;Former roommates are&lt;br&gt;Also&lt;br&gt;Available as reference.  &lt;br&gt;Thanks!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;</content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/mnh/abo/d/furnished-large-1-bedroom-apt/6657091517.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-08-05T08:56:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>