<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ParkSlope_Gowanus_DR.xml</id><title>ParkSlope_Gowanus_DR</title><updated>2019-01-25T22:59:42-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ParkSlope_Gowanus_DR.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in ParkSlope_Gowanus_DR</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/brooklyn-small-1-br-with-full-kitchen/6803810613.html</id><title>$2200  //  Small 1 BR with full kitchen in beautiful brownstone</title><updated>2019-01-25T16:31:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00r0r_g0m0Q3IurFw_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;Available Feb 15 or March 1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO WE'RE LOOKING FOR: A single person or couple who are feminist and queer friendly. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE BUILDING: This is a beautiful old brownstone on a quiet street in the heart of Park Slope. Owner is a semi-retired feminist lawyer who lives on the ground and parlor floors. She responds quickly to issues. There are three rental apartments upstairs. Animals are permitted on a case-by-case basis (there's a sweet dog living on the top floor). There is FREE WiFi for the whole building. There is no laundry available, but laundromat closeby. Heat and hot water provided. Gas (for stove) and electric are tenant's responsibilities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE APARTMENT: The apartment is a small one-bedroom. It is up two flights of stairs (one outside, one inside).    &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE LIVING ROOM: There is a spacious living room with big windows facing the street that let in good light. It has an exposed brick wall with an unusable but adorable fireplace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE KITCHEN: There is a full size kitchen with new stove and fridge. Can fit a dining table and actually sit down to eat. Has a large closet/pantry. Window overlooks the backyard. Note: Pictures show a dryer under the kitchen table, but there is no washer/dryer hookup.   &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE BATHROOM: The bathroom is decent sized. It has a full tub and shower. Original tiling.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE BEDROOM: The bedroom is small. It is an actual bedroom (this is not a studio) but is long and thin. It fits a full size bed on risers, as well as some space for one large or two small dressers. The bedroom has its own window with a nice view. There is some noise in the morning once or twice a week when the garbage collectors come around. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FURNITURE: Some of the furniture can be purchased from the outgoing tenant if desired.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;INTERESTED? Text Laura at  &lt;a href="/fb/nyc/abo/6803810613" class="showcontact" title="click to show contact info" rel="nofollow"&gt;show contact info&lt;/a&gt;. Texts are better than calls because I often can't get to the phone at work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prospective tenants pay $40 for a credit check, must provide paystub and references. Guarantor necessary if tenant makes less than 30x monthly rent.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00F0F_gxCtOl830Nw_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00k0k_6E0bPhcJGDr_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00Y0Y_cImDNal3C3e_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00Z0Z_dq9jK6AtG05_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00H0H_eQZtl8RHC1r_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01111_iBdDECRhJqD_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00t0t_hzz5sOMCbKi_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00808_1ghMDlueP8A_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00Q0Q_azOP89stmkP_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/brooklyn-small-1-br-with-full-kitchen/6803810613.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-25T16:31:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>