<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ProspectHeights_CrownHeightsNorth_245_A.xml</id><title>ProspectHeights_CrownHeightsNorth_245_A</title><updated>2019-01-20T16:09:57-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ProspectHeights_CrownHeightsNorth_245_A.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in ProspectHeights_CrownHeightsNorth_245_A</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/brooklynbr-in-beautiful-clinton-hill/6799428805.html</id><title>$2600  //  $2600, 1BR in beautiful Clinton Hill</title><updated>2019-01-20T10:11:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00p0p_eDsDsfHwO6g_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;I am looking for a reliable sub-leasee from February 1, 2019 through August 30, 2020.  You may be able to rent (or even buy) the apartment after that date.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rent for the 1-BR apartment is $2,600/month, and you would be responsible for the electricity and Wi-Fi expenses, too.  You would not be responsible for the gas or water expenses.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The apartment is located on the 10th floor of a beautifully manicured co-op campus in the Clinton Hill neighborhood of Brooklyn, NY.  The unit boasts a beautiful 180-degree skyline view, modern appliances, and essential furnishings (king-sized bed, multiple wardrobes, leather couch, bookshelves, and smart A/C units). All of the neighbors on the floor are super sweet, generous, and respectful of one another's privacy and comfort.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The building is monitored 24/7 by camera surveillance and an ample staff of patrol guards.  Enjoy building entry by wireless intercom and key fob, and elevator access makes the building ADA-compliant and wheelchair accessible.  Shared commercial laundry facilities are available in the basement.  Pets are welcome, too!!  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Situated within a queer-friendly and kid-friendly neighborhood marked by bustling retail, restaurants, parks, schools, the Barclay's Arena, cultural, and transportation outlets, you can do just about anything within a 1-mile radius.  You can also commute to Manhattan or Queens inside of 15 minutes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All applicants must be interviewed by the co-op board and pay related application fees.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please reply if you are serious about renting the apartment for at least 9 months, and would like to move forward with scheduling a viewing.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01515_gqUxQvwXgT1_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00W0W_7KDEy4wWbij_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00s0s_egYIaYOwzDZ_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00n0n_hdJrvxawJOe_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00G0G_dzbZRKQqZDg_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00S0S_j7iWG9QMUBe_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00K0K_kA2xx4EPR3y_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/brooklynbr-in-beautiful-clinton-hill/6799428805.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-20T10:11:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>