<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ProspectHeights_CrownHeightsNorth_245_A.xml</id><title>ProspectHeights_CrownHeightsNorth_245_A</title><updated>2019-01-16T01:05:29-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/ProspectHeights_CrownHeightsNorth_245_A.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in ProspectHeights_CrownHeightsNorth_245_A</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/brooklyn-huge-sunny-15br-huge-private/6795886466.html</id><title>$2299  //  Huge sunny 1.5BR huge private terrace parking available Prime C.Height</title><updated>2019-01-15T19:07:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01212_3Jqph6xxTrB_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;===\\\**^**^**^**NO FEE!!!**^**^**^**///===&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bright, beautifully renovated and loaded with all the extras you've been looking for!&lt;br&gt;Take advantage of this of this special opportunity to call this incredibly charming, residence your new home. This multi-family, red brick townhouse is situated on a quiet block just off Franklin Avenue which boasts arguably the best restaurants in Brooklyn and just 3 blocks from 2,3,4,5 &amp;amp; S trains which means you're only 20 minutes from Manhattan! You're also just a 5-minute walk to Prospect Park and the Botanic Garden so you can make both amazing destinations a regular part of your schedule when looking to unwind.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special features include a private, garaged parking space for a nominal fee, exclusive use of the front entrance terrace, tons of common storage space for your bike(s) and things. Get an early start on those dinner party invitations as the 150-foot, dining roomoffers plenty of space to entertain! Additional features include a recently renovated, chef's kitchen with stainless steel appliances, a tiled bathroom with newly appointed fixtures, beautiful hardwoods floors throughout and high ceilings. You'll be hard pressed to find all these amazing offerings at your typical, cookie cutter rental.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will go FAST!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call or text ONLY (no emails please) ==&amp;gt;&amp;gt;==&amp;gt;&amp;gt;//9:1:7|||7:9:2|||1:4:0:2\\&amp;lt;&amp;lt;==&amp;lt;&amp;lt;==    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00h0h_4N1vcdMTQAF_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00000_bMoVh43pnzv_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00l0l_50VcQ8aNbYV_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/brk/abo/d/brooklyn-huge-sunny-15br-huge-private/6795886466.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-15T19:07:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>