<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/UpperWest_12_BC.xml</id><title>UpperWest_12_BC</title><updated>2019-01-21T00:09:40-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/UpperWest_12_BC.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in UpperWest_12_BC</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/que/abo/d/2-bedroom-large-and-beautiful-apartment/6799720238.html</id><title>$2025  //  2 Bedroom - Large and Beautiful Apartment - St. John&amp;#39;s  University</title><updated>2019-01-20T18:00:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01616_22s1j143Sol_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;**February 1st Move-In Date&lt;br&gt;**Showing available immediately&lt;br&gt;**Pictures shown are of unit in same building. Available unit is carpeted &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spacious TWO-Bedroom/ONE Bathroom&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spacious and bright two bedrooms, one bathroom apartment close to all the essentials on the corner of 164th Street and 82nd Road; one block north of Grand Central Parkway and two blocks south of Union Turnpike. This is a convenient location for those working in Manhattan and students going to St. John's University. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amenities: &lt;br&gt;Water Included &lt;br&gt;Mirrored Closet Doors&lt;br&gt;Outdoor private balcony &lt;br&gt;Time Warner, Verizon FiOS, DirecTV ready. &lt;br&gt;In-Wall Heat &lt;br&gt;In-Wall AC Ready (You will never have to put your ac in your window.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dimensions: &lt;br&gt;1st Bedroom: 12'X12'&lt;br&gt;Larger bedroom will easily fit two Full beds for students. &lt;br&gt;2nd Bedroom: 10.5'X9' &lt;br&gt;One Full or Queen Bed and Dresser. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Area:&lt;br&gt;Located in a safe neighborhood with ample lighting in front of Queens Hospital Center. Cuisines include: Asian, American, Halal and others down the street. &lt;br&gt;There is ample parking located on 82nd Road. Walking distance to the cleaners, two Laundromats, food, gas stations. You are conveniently located at express stops for the Q65 (in front of apartment), Q46 (164th Street/Union Turnpike) as well as QM1/5/6/7/8 (164th Street/Union Turnpike). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sample Commute Times:&lt;br&gt;10 minutes walking to St. John's University Gate 6&lt;br&gt;15 minutes walking to Parsons F Train&lt;br&gt;42 minutes public transportation to Midtown Manhattan via Q65/F or Q46/E,F &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br&gt;Q46 from Kew Gardens (E/F -- Kew Gardens) to Springfield Boulevard, Glen Oaks, Long Island Jewish &lt;br&gt;Q65 from Jamaica (E -- Jamaica Center AirTrain JFK, LIRR, F -- Parsons Boulevard) to College Point (7 -- Main Street) &lt;br&gt;QM1/5/6 to Midtown Express&lt;br&gt;QM7/8 to Downtown Express &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please contact me at  &lt;a href="/fb/nyc/abo/6799720238" class="showcontact" title="click to show contact info" rel="nofollow"&gt;show contact info&lt;/a&gt; with any questions, showings taking place now!    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00101_CgTCqkQTvA_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00I0I_9R3q8b91Uhc_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00n0n_fe5cB7K7tAz_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/que/abo/d/2-bedroom-large-and-beautiful-apartment/6799720238.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-20T18:00:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>