<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/Woodside_MR.xml</id><title>Woodside_MR</title><updated>2019-01-20T18:31:31-05:00</updated><author><name>Ben Snell</name></author><link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bensnell/apts-nyc/master/Woodside_MR.xml" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.7.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>NYC 2BR Apartment Listings in Woodside_MR</subtitle><entry><id>https://newyork.craigslist.org/que/abo/d/astoria-recently-renovated-spacious-1/6799460992.html</id><title>$1750  //  Recently Renovated, Spacious 1 Bdrm-1/2 blk to subway-Utilities Inc (W</title><updated>2019-01-20T12:37:00-05:00</updated><content type="html">&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01212_irGEieXNc37_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;p&gt;Listing is for a spacious 1 bedroom BASEMENT apartment for rent in a quiet and residential neighborhood in Woodside, Queens. NO BROKER FEES.&lt;br&gt;Apartment was gut renovated just a few years ago and is well maintained. &lt;br&gt;Please note listing price does not include furniture that is pictured. Apartment will be empty, however, if interested can negotiate to include furniture as well.&lt;br&gt;$1,750 Rent includes utilities (heat, water, electricity). Apartment is available immediately.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; There are windows in the living room as well as bedroom (see pictures). It is super close (half a block only) to the R/M Norther Blvd subway stop (subway is at the end of the same block as the house). A quick 15-20 minutes ride gets you into midtown Manhattan. Also have access to other train lines (E, F, 7) including express lines by taking the subway 2 stops further into Queens to Jackson heights/Roosevelt avenue. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Entire apartment was gut renovated just a few years ago with modern high end finishes and is very well maintained. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; - Spacious Kitchen/Living Room with 2 windows providing plenty of natural light. Kitchen with stainless steel appliances, granite countertop, huge sink, European style cabinets with soft close feature. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; - Big modern bathroom with rain shower head, Kohler toilet, glass mosaic tiles and other sleek fixtures. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; - Large bedroom with a closet and 2 windows providing natural light. 2 big his/hers closets in the hallway. Recessed lighting in the entire apartment. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Not your typical tiny rental apartment made of poor quality cheap material. This is a rarely found gem in a great location...1/2 block to subway, close to Steinway area restaurants &amp;amp; bars as well as plethora of ethnic food restaurants in Jackson Heights/Elmhurst, close to Manhattan, shopping, highways, airports, etc. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Monthly Rent: $1750 (includes all utilities such as heating, water &amp;amp; electricity). NO BROKER FEES&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; MAX 2 occupants. Sorry NO pets allowed. Quiet neighborhood with lovely families around so no party animals please. Should be able to supply good reference letter from current landlord, pay stub/proof of employment &amp;amp; credit report. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Apartment is available immediately.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01616_kxN3jwsa7wj_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00909_d3x7QYS5oxl_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00n0n_4GwkZuklTNj_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01111_dLjxzHcmK8A_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00E0E_hh2yhNbSmoR_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00P0P_2gAwn2mWel0_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00t0t_396vqvomsBD_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00b0b_gTVCRRsSkGz_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00m0m_1Y4ILdMN791_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00m0m_dirWDomm5Uv_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00202_hZlHQC154pR_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/01313_7LdnXFBIMrD_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00r0r_lN78YdrtAix_600x450.jpg" /&gt; &lt;img src="https://images.craigslist.org/00404_guEsb7EMOKD_600x450.jpg" /&gt; </content><link href="https://newyork.craigslist.org/que/abo/d/astoria-recently-renovated-spacious-1/6799460992.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-20T12:37:00-05:00</published></entry></feed>